From the paragraph toolbar, you can also
insert further types of content,
cue-2
such as tables, images, and YouTube
videos.
cue-3
To insert a table, click Insert Table.
cue-4
This creates an empty table with a
two-by-two default size.
cue-5
Clicking any cell of the table brings up a
three vertical dots menu button in that
cue-6
cell.
cue-7
Click the button to bring up the table
editing menu.
cue-8
From the table menu, you can add and
delete rows and columns, format a table,
cue-9
delete the table, and so on.
cue-10
But you cannot copy-paste tables from
other resources.
cue-11
For accessibility, remember to use the
toggle header option for any row or column
cue-12
headers in your table
cue-13
so that they can be read correctly by a
screen reader.
cue-14
If your table needs a caption, you can
enter one by clicking Caption (Optional)
cue-15
below your table.
cue-16
To insert an image, in the paragraph
toolbar, click Insert Image.
cue-17
An image placeholder will appear.
cue-18
Click the Choose Image button to select,
upload, or indicate the image you want to
cue-19
insert.
cue-20
If you select the wrong image or want to
change the image later, click Select Image
cue-21
in the image toolbar to return to the
Select Image overlay.
cue-22
You can only add images from the image
upload menu.
cue-23
To upload other types of media,
cue-24
go to the audio or video upload menus.
cue-25
Click Settings in the image toolbar to
bring up the image setting overlays.
cue-26
Here, you can optionally adjust the size
of your image.
cue-27
You can also enter alternative text for
your image.
cue-28
For accessibility, remember to add a
meaningful image description in the
cue-29
alternative text for all non-purely
decorative images.
cue-30
As with tables, if your image needs a
caption, you can enter one by clicking
cue-31
Caption (Optional) below your image.
cue-32
To insert other kinds of content, click
the
cue-33
plus insert icon in the paragraph toolbar
and select the kind of content you want to
cue-34
insert. For example, to insert a YouTube
video,
cue-35
click YouTube and enter the video's URL in
the overlay.